Hello Hello Friends Welcome back to my
YouTube channel Tax in Finance Friends
in today's video we will talk
about ICICI Bank limit Yes friends
ICICI Bank Police Quarter One
result is going to come tomorrow so let's take a
look at what the result is tomorrow Okay first of all
we have read the article which has been
published by Business Standard
that ICICI Bank Quarter One profit
jump 60% year on year on air states sale in
insurance mango exports Experts have
said that its quarter one
profit can be seen 60%
Okay and we have also seen earlier
when the results of HDFC Bank and ICICI Bank came
Khatauni Axis Bank came then
their results were also good so let's move ahead
about this article that
now as you can see here the current market
share of ICICI Bank is
31.05
Okay
yesterday swimming of its position as one of the
strongest private players, as
you know ICICI  The bank is considered to be a very
strong private sector company
in the banking sector. ICICI Bank has
clocked up to 60% growth in
net profit at Rs
300,108 crore in the April to June
quarter of financial year 21A. It is being
said that
its profit may see a 60% jump
in this quarter.
Now, let's move ahead. What is being said is that these shares,
which are ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance and
ICICI Lombard, are its light functions
and status. I am saying that the bank is
scheduled to release its results on Saturday, July
25th. Yes friends, the result of the bank
elections 2014 is going to come, that is, when the market is
closed on Saturday at this time, Sunday will also be closed on Monday.
What will be its impact on the market? The
sentiment is completely positive. At
this time, this stock has
not even risen as much as others like
ICICI, Axis Bank, HDFC etc.  From the
results of and so all this is quite good, all this has
risen, so this is a good opportunity for me,
if you do intraday trading in the morning then you
can do it, and for those who did it, it is a
good thing because they can
take advantage of the gap opening,
if we talk about however with
rapid growth reduction
activity of T20 lockdown and cutting
marginal cost of Baroda and lending rate, it has been
seen from Vinay that
yes, the group is a little weak,
but it is okay that in this quarter,
little by little, the search is slowly
coming back on track, now see, as you must have
heard the name of Akshay
Expect Share Khana, how much has he
expressed, expect the land to
clock a net profit of Rs 108 crore,
register growth and 63 per cent on a
profit of 108 crore, which for the quarter dynasty,
in a functionality in twenty,
said from a cotton 000, okay,
I would say that 63 per cent growth can be seen
if we look at quarterly  If we talk about the basis, even if we
forget the country, the profit margin is 54.6%.
Ansh of the share market said so.
Okay, Darpan Shade tracking the
Sector-8 HDFC Securities mean
daily net profit margin is lower left in the
range of pristine 2%. The
Aniston head of HDFC Securities
said that according to him it can increase by 22%.
Okay, so you can see that there is
sentiment everywhere.
All the analysts say that whatever its share price
goes, it will be positive, meaning it will increase. Okay, the
festival in higher provision now 271
persons or BDOs of royalty and cotton from the pan, the
bank is proactively utilizing game from
stake sales in subsidiaries.
He said that a lot of stake was sold, so they
also have wheat and
optimistic estimate from them.
Okay, okay, if we talk here about
98 Nirmal Bank Institutional Equities
pack the profit of forex now that ping 101
11005 cent your near end quarter  228 Now
as you can see, Nirmal Bank
Institutional Equities has
said that this can rise by 10%.
Share Airways is in the lower end list. Clip
Capital Express, the net profit growth is
just 50%. If we look at the low flame, till
now we have shown it on the higher site
because see, 50% is being
estimated here. Okay, we
expect Dabangg to create a contingent
provision and 1800 crore for the
quarter under review. It is believed
that provisioning will be made in Gangster.
Whatever free MP etc., all this was
due to beer, so it is expected
that the bank can do a project of 1800 crore.
Okay,
now let us talk further about loan book and
interest income. So let us look at this.
I have listed on average expected bank
credit growth trimmed restricted to
single digit. It is being
said that the
credit growth of the bank will remain restricted
in single digit, that is, we will expect 9
percent.  This is being talked about near road
okay
in this video securities in you must have heard your name how
to release date
that if you lose of take good between fennel and dish
for the quarter deposit growth is always
strong
that nature of a
given on business net interest income the
difference between interest and explained
net interest income this is what you have done
and what you have explained so by
adding jail what came is net interest income
you all that is being seen that Guru will do
1516 per sent a year after year it is being
believed so to
connect with interest margin this is sim sim coming down from
3.7 per cent
which was seen in the quarter for that
if we talk about net interest margin then
you can see here
yes their net interest margin will be
3.7 per cent and that is
known from the previous quarter
find it okay let's
talk about acid quality and key monitors
Jeevan Dam Auditorium Extended  By
RBI David, the quality of the bank
remains stable and higher slippages on
subsequent current basis. Okay, analysts'
capital estimate is 3802 posting the
contraction of 28.47 quarter on quarter from 10
crores. Okay, and if we
talk about daily basis, it is 36.7 percent.
9th monitoring bill is downgraded by 2000
China Rapid Action,
their rating has
also been tripled, they are
saying this after downloading. Okay, as per the Adult Food Security
Scheme, Bigg Boss and Pihu show will
remain tablet 5.5 which will be the anti-issue. It is
expected that it will remain stable
and will improve and improve up-on a year on year
from 0.5%. Okay, so
friends, here you see
what has been said in the last, during a quarter
under review,
bank stocks and performance Reddy
Bourse 14.38, stock price of ICICI
Bank Advance 8.3 percent  There is a
rise in S&P BSE Sensex at 18.4.
As you all know that
due to the lockdown, many banks in the banking
sector have underperformed. So
now what is happening now gradually, as the
unlocking is happening, everything is coming back
on track. So gradually now things are getting better, so
you are fine again. Therefore, it is
expected that the bank results from today can be
positive. A
good growth can be seen. So
if you people want, you
can take interest in it. Okay, you
can get interested in the morning and as soon as the market opens,
you can see that the fiber will be applied.
Okay, friends, this was the
article news related to the bank. So
friends, I hope you liked this video.
If you liked this video, then please
subscribe to my channel
and like this video. Thank you.